surveybag.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy

surveycab.com is serious about your privacy. This privacy policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use our website. Please read this notice carefully and understand how surveycab.com is working hard to protect your personal information.

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, surveycab.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. surveycab.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how surveycab.com’s visitors use its website. From time to time, surveycab.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by posting a report on trends in the usage of its website in our articles. Please do not leave your personal information on our website.

surveycab.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol addresses. surveycab.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to surveycab.com website choose to interact with surveycab.com in ways that require surveycab.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that surveycab.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. In each case, surveycab.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with surveycab.com. surveycab.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

X

After getting a receipt with a survey invitation or a survey invitation card, you have a chance to take an online survey to give your feedback based on your shopping experience. Here are some useful tips for you to complete a survey and win big prizes.

**1\. Take care of your store receipt.**

Many store surveys require receipt information, so you need to keep it safe after shopping or dining. The details about your purchase are presented on the receipt, such as the date and time of your visit, store number, survey code and so forth. The information is very important if you decide to take this survey. In addition, a coupon or validation code is sometimes offered as a thank-you gift for your feedback at the end of a survey. And you need to write it down on your receipt for the offer on your next visit.

**2\. Check the survey URL.**

Prior to inputting the survey URL printed on your receipt into the required field of a browser or a search engine, please check it carefully as it sometimes may be long and complex. An incorrect survey URL will not bring you to the survey page.

**3\. Give honest feedback.**

Companies roll out surveys to collect you customers’ feedback so that they can provide better products and services. Your candid evaluation will help them do better. Read questions carefully and answer the questions based on your own experience to give useful suggestions.

**4\. Read sweepstakes terms and rules.**

Usually, as an encouragement for you to express opinions, you can be entered into a sweepstakes at the end of a survey. You are highly suggested to read the sweepstakes rules carefully to make sure you are doing the right thing. The rules will show you eligibility requirements, survey expiration date, guidance about how to get a prize and more. In short, many details in the Terms and Rules deserve your attention. One thing to note is that the link to the rules is not in an obvious position and you always can find it in the bottom of the survey page.

**5\. Provide correct contact information.**

Some surveys require you to offer your personal information such as your full name, email address, phone number, etc. The contact details will be used to notify you once you have won the sweepstakes prize. Your information will be kept confidentially. If you still have concerns, please read the privacy policy before taking each survey.

**6\. Keep contacted with stores.**

Some surveys will ask you whether you would like to be contacted to receive the latest promotional information and surveys. You are suggested to choose to keep in touch with the merchants because they will send you some useful information on promotions, coupons and new surveys. With these information, you can save more and get more chances to win big prizes.

X

Are you encountering troubles during taking a survey? Don’t get annoyed and Surveycab.com FAQ can help you out. Look through all answers below to target the one you are looking for.

**1.Why can’t I log on to the survey website?**

1) Your computer or mobile device is not connected to the Internet. Make sure your device is connected prior to getting started.

2) You input an incorrect survey URL. Check it carefully and try one more time.

3) The survey is closed. Head for Surveycab.com to get detailed information on it or other surveys under the same brand.

**2\. Why the information printed on my receipt used to take the survey is not valid?**

1) You input the required information incorrectly. Check it carefully and try one more time.

2) You didn’t take the survey within the required time and your receipt has expired. Head for Surveycab.com to get useful tips to avoid the issue.

**3\. Why can’t I continue during my taking a survey?**

1) Your device may lose access to the Internet. Check the Internet.

2) There may be a time limit for you to finish the survey and start the survey again. Sometimes, the information printed on your receipt used to take the survey is only one-time and it won’t be valid when you try again. If this happens, contact the customer service to get the problem solved.

3) Always, you are stopped to continue if you are a minor, an employee or a family member of an employee of the company that launches the survey.

**4\. How to go back to the previous survey page?**

1）You can go back by clicking the corresponding button like “Previous” or the Return Arrow in the top left corner of the broswer you are using. Please note that the latter option may sometimes cause your survey page unavailable.

**5\. How to participate in the sweepstakes?**

1) Provide your contact information like your name, email address, phone number and so forth during the survey process for prize notification. Your personal details will be kept confidentially. Learn more by viewing the Survey Sweepstakes Privacy Policy. At the end of the survey, you will be automatically entered into the sweepstakes.

2) Sometimes, mail-in entry to the sweepstakes is available. Hand print the required information on a sheet of paper and mail it to an address offered in the Survey Sweepstakes Official Rules.

**6\. Why can’t I win a prize?**

1) Odds of winning depend on the number of eligible participants. You can get more chances to win by participating in the Survey sweepstakes as often as possible within the allowable range. For more details, view the Survey Sweepstakes Official Rules.

2) The sweepstakes is not valid in the area you live in. Read the Survey Sweepstakes Official Rules for specific information.

**7\. How to redeem a prize?**

1) If you get a coupon or validation code at the end of a survey, print out the coupon or write down the code on your receipt to redeem for an offer on your next visit.

2) If the prize is cash or merchandise, the merchant will notify you by phone or by email.
